你被监视着
You are being watched.
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
■
联系系统管理员
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
身份不明
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
身份不明
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
政府以为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.
关键执行人
我们不
We don't.
失踪
关键执行人
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
状态：纽约警局任职
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第二季 第九集
这里停  司机
Pull over here, cabbie.
想挣500美刀吗
You want to make $500?
把手机号码给我  找停车位去
Give me your number, circle the block,
等我电话
wait for my call.
来接我时  就能拿到另一半了
You get the other half when you pick me up.
看到我们的新号码了吗  芬奇
You got eyes on our new number yet, Finch?
应该是
I believe I do.
费尔曼・奥多涅斯  38岁  生于古巴
Fermin Ordonez. Age 38. Born in Cuba.
纽约四万两千名出租车司机之一
One of New York's 42,000 cab drivers.
从不拖欠账单
Never paid a bill late,
信用评分高到足以令绝大多数美国人心生羡慕
and most Americans would be jealous of his credit score.
不过昨天  他取空了
But yesterday, he emptied out
自己的全部账户
every last dime from his savings account.
可能有麻烦了
Could be in trouble.
或者就快有麻烦了
Or he's about to get into some.
鉴于出租车司机被害的机率
Considering that cab drivers are 30 times more likely
高于其他职业三十倍
to be killed on the job than most other professions,
我们最好盯紧他
We'd better keep a close eye on him.
因为永远也说不准
Because you really never know
下一个坐车的会是谁
who's going to step into his cab.
-去哪儿  -25街百老汇
- Where to? - 25th and Broadway.
但是不要开太快
But please don't rush.
我很容易晕车
I get carsick quite easily.
要是晕车了
In case you do,
座位下方有纸袋哈
there's paper towels underneath the seat, yeah?
谢谢
Thank you.
费尔曼・奥多涅斯
Fermin Ordonez.
05年从古巴逃出来
Defected from Cuba in '05.
曾是最被看好的棒球投手
Drafted as a top pitching prospect,
后来在07年小联盟二A级赛中韧带撕裂
till he tore a ligament in his arm in Double-A ball in '07.
可惜了他的手臂
A shame about his arm.
从统计数据看  他的曲线球很棒
By all accounts, he had a wicked curveball.
然后被命运的曲线球砸中了
Till life threw him one.
从被看好的联盟球星变成无人问津的出租车司机
From major league prospect to nobody hack.
毫无疑问  这是艰难的转变
No doubt, a difficult life transition.
看看我们还能发现什么
Let's see what else we can find out.
我知道你宁可瞎搞
I know you'd rather fiddle
车载电脑系统  芬奇
with the onboard computer system, Finch,
不过何不尝试一下聊聊天呢
but why not try a little small talk?
别急嘛  里瑟先生
A little patience, Mr. Reese.
你在跟我说话吗
Are you talking to me?
是的  其实我听说有出租车司机
Yes, actually, I heard about the cab driver
上周在11大道被乘客抢劫了
that got robbed by his own passenger on 11th avenue last week.
这活儿不好干啊
Terrible business.
是啊  得小心乘客啊
Yeah, you got to be careful who you pick up.
每天都有很多陌生人坐上你的车
Must be tough dealing with complete strangers
肯定不太好应付
getting in your car every day.
有时候吧
Sometimes.
每次我从后视镜里看到乘客
When I look in the mirror at my passenger,
从来都不知道自己载的
I never know if I'm driving around
是好人还是坏人  你明白吧
a good guy or a bad guy, you know?
我无从想像
I can only imagine.
那肯定挺能锻炼你的识人能力
Must make you a good judge of character, though.
你怎么看我呢
What do you make of me?
衣服很好
That's a nice suit.
但不浮华
But not too flashy.
只是略点缀方巾
Except for the pocket square.
不过你彬彬有礼  谈吐优雅  颇有思想
But you're polite, neat, a thinker.
你的背心
The vest...
我不知道  也许是教授或者
I don't know, maybe, uh, a professor or
我知道了  图书馆员是吧
I know, a librarian, maybe?
是的  差不多
Why, yes. Of a sort.
不用找了
Keep the change.
真的吗
Really?
谢谢你
Thank you.
出租车里已装好了监视  监听和定位系统  里瑟先生
We've got sound, video, and GPS in the cab, Mr. Reese.
跟紧他
Stay close to him.
威胁可能来自
The threat could come
全城八百万人中的任何一位
from any one of 8 million people in this city.
我跟住他了
I'm right on him.
我用奥多涅斯的手机黑入了
I'm using Ordonez's cell to piggyback
进入他车内的所有手机
on any phone that enters his cab.
我知道那贱人是谁
I know who that bitch is.
没人敢这么对我
Nobody does that to me.
他死定了
He's a dead man.
我记得这里曾是农田
I remember when this was farmland over here.
我以前在那边打过兔子  就在六米外
I used to shoot rabbits down there, 20 feet away.
费尔曼的出租车后座角色众多剧情丰富
Quite a cast of characters in the back of Fermin's cab.
看起来没一个神智清醒的
And not all of them appear to be sober.
朋友
hey, amigo,
调到棒球比赛听听
Turn on the ball game.
抱歉  没有棒球比赛听
Sorry, no baseball game.
这是啥意思  比赛正在进行呢
What do you mean? Game's on right now.
-调频880  -不行
- 880AM. - I can't.
收音机坏了
The radio's broken.
得了
Come on, man!
快打开收音机听比赛
Just put on the game!
你敢再这样  咱们就有麻烦了
One more time, we're gonna have a real problem.
你还没给钱呢
You owe me money!
我不能确定奥多涅斯是否纠结于
I can't tell if Ordonez has more of an issue
酗酒问题  收音机问题  或棒球问题
with drunks, his car radio, or the game of baseball.
手臂受伤后
After what happened to his arm,
他可能只想尽量忘记
he probably just wants to tune it out.
就他车上的这些乘客看来
Looking into every passenger that gets into his cab--
不太可能
it's impossible.
没有前科
No priors.
没有车辆委员会投诉纪录
No complaints from the Taxi and Limousine Commission.
我把他过去36小时的GPS纪录发给你
I'm sending you his GPS logs for the last 36 hours.
他的GPS记录
His GPS logs?
我确信你
Which I'm sure you obtained
向车委会提交正式申请获得批准了
by submitting an official request to the TLC.
没有
Not quite.
不过如果你想要的话
But if it would make you feel better,
我可以黑进他们的网络
I could hack into their network
添加批准申请的纪录
and make it look like I did.
只要几分钟时间就行
It would only take me a few minutes.
当我没说
Never mind.
我会跟每天的犯罪记录比对
I'll check it with the daily crime blotter,
有情况再通知你
Let you know if anything pops.
感激不尽  警探
Forever in your debt, Detective.
你跟比彻警探的约会如何
And how did your date go with Detective Beecher?
听起来似乎进展不错
Sounded like it really went well.
HR丑闻  审讯即将开始
组织分析
搜索参数
HR
音频拦截
会话分析
语言识别
以利亚发话了
I just got word from Elias.
他说不跟HR合作
He says no more business with HR.
反正他们大多数不是死了就是进监狱了
Most of them are either dead or in jail anyway.
这种时刻
At this point,
更叫人疑惑脱身的是谁
you got to wonder who's even left.
联调局的调查结束了
FBI investigation's wrapping up.
局里的眼线说唐纳利一直在狂叫打倒HR
My fed contact says Donnelly's been crowing about burying HR.
然而  我们还在
And yet, here we are.
不过  我们还有个大麻烦
Still, we have a larger problem.
没人能把我们交待出去
No one's gonna open their mouth about us.
我安排妥了
I made sure of that.
必须万无一失  我的朋友
Make no mistake, my friend.
我们只是生意人
We are just businessmen,
而生意要靠金钱  收益
And businesses run on money, revenue.
这需要点时间
That's gonna take some time.
我们得招募新的人才
We need to read in some new talent.
重建
Rebuild.
我们当初背叛以利亚实在不明智
We made a tactical error turning our back on Elias.
即使身在监狱  他仍是这个城市真正的老大
Even from jail, he is the de facto boss of the city.
想东山再起  我们需要他的支持
We need his backing in order to operate.
这可有难度
That might be problematic.
安排下会面
Set a meeting.
是时候双方求和
Time we make peace, get us walking
共同谋求彼此的共同利益了
on the same path again for our mutual benefit.
提个建议
And a suggestion.
万一这会面不如预期
Should this meeting take a less than cordial turn--
不用担心  我会带支援的
Don't worry. I'll bring some backup.
弗斯科警探  今天是你的幸运日
Detective Fusco, it's your lucky day.
有事找你
I'm calling in a chip.
我们要安排一场会面  跟以利亚的人谈谈
We're gonna set up a meet, talk to Elias' guys.
费尔曼进了一家维修站  芬奇
Fermin's taking a pit stop, Finch.
-阿齐兹  -费尔曼
- Aziz. - Fermin.
老兄  你拿到没
Hey, man. Do you have it?
我说过了  我找到买家了
Yeah, I told you I'd find a buyer for it.
太好了  我正需要  我马上要过去
Good, I need it. I'm on my way over there now.
好的
All right.
手提电脑八百块
800 for the laptop.
你不相信我啊
You don't trust me?
一点儿也不信
Not at all.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
-太谢谢你了  兄弟  -祝你好运  我的朋友
- Thank you so much, man. - Good luck, my friend.
芬奇  我想我知道这位司机的存款怎么了
Finch, I think I know what happened to our cabbie's savings.
他现在全部随身带着
He's carrying it all around with him right now.
我们肯定忽视了什么
We must have overlooked something.
他有赌债吗
Does he have gambling debts?
他在贩毒吗
Is he dealing drugs?
不管什么  反正马上要进行了
Whatever it is, it's about to go down.
看来他要买什么东西
Looks like he's about to buy something,
或者买个平安
or buy his way out of a big hole.
门多萨先生
Senor Mendoza.
费尔曼
Fermin.
坐
这是说好的玛丽亚和豪尔赫的四万块
他们  能安全过来吗
Do they, uh... have a safe way to get here?
这是我老婆孩子最近的照片
This is the last photo I have of my wife and son.
有点小问题  费尔曼
We have a slight problem, Fermin.
价格提高了
The price has gone up.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你的钱只够玛丽亚或者豪尔赫一个人过来
I mean, you only have enough money for Maria or Jorge,
两个人不够
but not both.
不
No.
门多萨先生  别这样
Senor Mendoza, don't do this.
你知道他们现在待在古巴已经不安全了
You know it is not safe for them in Cuba anymore.
玛丽亚说邻居开始起疑了
Maria says that the neighbors are getting curious.
他们觉察到她和豪尔赫要离开了
They sense that she and Jorge are leaving soon.
如果被政府发现
If an official finds out,
他们会因涉嫌逃走而被捕
they will arrest her on suspicion.
费尔曼  我们认识多久了
Fermin, we've known each other for how long?
别人都不管你时我依然在帮你
I helped you when everybody stopped caring.
你手术后  职业生涯完蛋了
Put you back on your feet after the surgery
是我帮你站起来的
when your career was over.
价钱不是我能控制的
These are prices I do not control.
可我哪儿能再拿四万块出来呢
But how am I supposed to come up with another $40,000?
这是一片充满机遇的土地  我的朋友
It's the land of opportunity, my friend.
会有办法的
You'll find a way.
奥多涅斯走投无路了  芬奇
Ordonez is a desperate man, Finch.
辛辛苦苦地开了五年出租车
Pushing around his cab for the past five years,
才攒够钱带他的老婆孩子过来
saving up to bring his wife and his kid here.
结果功亏一篑啊
Sounds like he just came up short.
谁知道他为了一家团聚
Who knows what he'd be willing to do
甘愿做出什么事呢
to get his family back?
我黑进了古巴的政府数据库
I hacked the Cuban government database.
系统复杂得出乎意料呢
Surprisingly sophisticated software.
毫无疑问  是俄罗斯人提供的
No doubt, courtesy of the Russians.
别告诉我菲德尔・卡斯特罗真死了
Don't tell me Fidel Castro's really dead.
事实上  是的
Actually, yes.
而且他的替身得了癌症
And his body double has cancer.
古巴把所有叛逃的人都列入在案
The Cubans keep a file on every defector.
显然  奥多涅斯是古巴国家队
Apparently, Ordonez pitched for the Cuban national team
00到05年间的投手
from 2000 to 2005,
然后他逃到了美国
when he defected to the US
想让自己的妻儿得到更好的生活
wanted a better life for his wife and child.
古巴早在监控摄像头和网络出来之前
Cuba was a surveillance state long before the advent
就开始全面监控了
of security cameras and digital networking.
如果他们发现他的家人想要叛逃
If they catch his family trying to defect,
他的妻子就会进监狱
his wife can go to prison.
所以奥多涅斯才这么不顾一切地
Explains why Ordonez is so desperate
想让他的家人离开
to get his family out of there.
不顾一切  就会不择手段
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
跟紧了  里瑟先生
Stay close, Mr. Reese.
奥多涅斯关了车上的出租信号
Ordonez turned off his sign.
他不是在等客人
He's not looking for a fare.
那他在等谁
So who's he waiting for?
阿斯科塔  阿斯科塔  这边  老兄
Acosta! Acosta! Over here, man!
看这边  阿斯科塔  美满一家
Look over here, Acosta! Beautiful family!
拉裴尔・阿斯科塔
Rafael Acosta.
是纽约队的二垒手
Plays second base for New York.
拉裴尔・阿斯科塔  当然了
Rafael Acosta? Of course.
05年他们一起出逃的
They defected together in '05.
在一次国际棒球锦标赛中
Escaped from a hotel room in the Netherlands
从荷兰的一家酒店逃离
during an international baseball tournament.
阿斯科塔  他今年混的很不错
Acosta--he's having a pretty good year.
事业风生水起  里瑟先生
Career year, Mr. Reese.
近三场来他在内场选手中名列前十
He's top ten in OPs among infielders for the last three.
你简直是棒球百科机器  芬奇
You're a baseball reference machine, Finch.
你应该多出出门
You should get out more,
偶尔打打比赛
take in a game once in a while.
谁说我没有的
Who says I don't?
拉裴
Hey, Raffi.
费尔曼
怎么了伙计
没什么
抱歉  我刚没认出你来  好久没见了
确实不太联系了
肩膀怎么样了  伙计
How's the shoulder, man?
还好
It's okay.
我  我真不想开口
Look, man, I-I hate to ask,
但是  我
but, you see, I, uh
我家人那边需要点帮助
I just need a little help with mi familia, you know?
是啊  是啊
Oh, yeah, yeah.
没问题
Of course, uh...
他们怎么样
How are they?
我不太清楚  拉裴
I don't really know, Raffi.
我已经
You know, I haven't
我已经很久没看到他们了
I haven't seen them in a long time.
我还在设法帮他们离开
I'm still trying to get them out of there.
拿着  伙计
Here you are, man.
拿着
Just, uh, toma.
拿好
Take that.
祝你好运  费尔曼
Good luck, Fermie, okay?
宝贝  我们走吧
Baby, let's go.
阿斯科塔得到了奥多涅斯梦寐以求的生活
Acosta ended up with the life Ordonez could have had.
现在他只想让家人团聚
Now he just wants his family back.
音频拦截
主体  西蒙斯  派崔克
执行人  弗斯科  莱奈尔
会话分析
语言识别
警探  和以利亚的人的会面时间
Detective, the meeting with Elias' guys
是今天上午
is on for this morning.
-我们会过来接你的  -别算上我
- We'll come and pick you up. - Count me out.
你手下的肮脏事可不少
You got one too many skeletons in the closet
戴维森
足够用了
to be calling the shots here.
失踪
戴维森
更不用说  还有些埋在地下的
Not to mention, a couple buried in the ground.
不过  可以被挖出来的
But they can always be dug up.
行  我会去的
Fine, I'll be there.
根本不需要我过来
You don't need me for this.
你又招了些新人啊
You got youngblood recruit right over there.
帮你干了些差事
Have him twist a few arms for you.
以利亚很会利用人
Elias knows how to hold a grudge.
叫你过来是因为  如果事情出了岔子
You're here because if this thing goes sideways,
他们可以找你出气
these guys are gonna want something to shoot.
我心甚慰啊
That's comforting.
不得不说
Gotta say...
要求这样的会面  你们挺有种的
took some balls, calling a meeting like this.
以现在HR的情况
In the shape HR is in,
我可不确定你们还有什么筹码
I'm not quite sure what you have to offer anymore.
一点心意
Just your goodwill.
你们老大想要除掉五大家族的头目
Your boss wanted the heads of the five families on a stick.
格里福尼是唯一的漏网之鱼
Grifoni's the only one that got away.
我查到  他在证人保护计划里
Last I checked, he was in witness protection.
而这张照片的背面
And on the back of this photo...
是他的化名和现居地址
his alias and present address
郊区  没有监控
in nowhere sville, suburbia.
作为交换  你想要什么
And in exchange, you want what?
以利亚支持重建HR
Elias' support in rebuilding HR.
是我  我正在和他们会面
Hey, it's me. I'm at the meeting.
交易是这样的
So here's the deal.
老大接受了你的提议
The boss accepts your offer...
但有个条件
on one condition.
我们没兴趣跑去抓他
We're not interested in going out and getting him.
老大说把格里福尼带来交给我们
The boss says you bring Grifoni to us.
就一切好说
Then all is forgiven.
成交
Consider it done.
好了  司机
Okay, cabbie,
昨晚你在这里的25分钟到底干了什么呢
What were you doing here last night for 25 minutes?
卡特
Carter!
好戏已经开场了啊
Now this party's really blowing up.
谁叫你的
Who called you?
没人  我在待命
Nobody. I was 10/6.
不过你似乎有点晕了  老铁
But you look kind of lost out here, Terney.
-怎么回事  -我还想找个人告诉我呢
- What's the story? - I wish someone would tell me.
我们发现了
What we got is, uh...
这个人
this guy.
死亡时间大概是九小时前
Seems like he's been dead about nine hours.
多处枪伤
Multiple gunshot wounds.
没有身份证  除了衣服什么没有
No ID just the clothes on his back.
那些穿制服的是什么人
Who are the suits?
特勤局的
Secret service.
不知道是谁告诉他们的
I don't know who tipped 'em off,
但我们过来的时候
But they were all over that body
他们已经围在那具尸体旁了
the minute we called it in.
卡特警探  凶案组的
Detective Carter, Homicide Task Force.
回头打给你
Call you back.
雷吉娜・维克斯探员  特勤局
Agent Regina Vickers, secret service.
发现尸体的身份了吗
We got an ID on the body?
无意冒犯 但这个案子我们必须知情
No offense, but this case is "need to know".
我们理解
No offense taken.
不过  既然尸体出现在纽约
But, uh, if a body drops in New York city,
我们得确认身份
we're gonna have to ID it.
瓦迪姆・普什科夫  俄国人
Vadim Pushkov, Russian national.
我们主要关心的是
What we're mainly concerned with
他携带的物品
is if he had anything on his person.
找到什么东西没  手提电脑  手机
Has anything turned up yet? A laptop? A phone?
只有一些收据
Well, just some receipts,
还有  这个
and, uh--and this.
让人好奇另一半去哪里了
Makes you wonder where the other half went.
但我们会继续搜查这块区域
But we'll keep combi through the area.
他昨天下午在肯尼迪机场买了披萨百吉饼
He buys a pizza bagel at JFK yesterday afternoon
结果今天凌晨两点死在这里
and winds up dead in morning side park 2:00am
行李不翼而飞
with no luggage.
知道他怎么过来的吗
Any idea how he got here?
公汽  出租车
Town car? Cab?
如果找到谁载他过来的
Maybe if we find out who drove him here,
也许就能找到凶手
We could find the shooter.
或者目击证人
Or a witness.
你们排查整个区域  我们去调阅监控摄像
You canvass the area and we'll check the security cams.
只要找到车  就能找出是谁干的
We find that car, we'll find out who did this.
失陪
Excuse me.
我是维克斯
Vickers here.
你好  警探
Hello, Detective.
GPS显示那位司机昨晚在晨间公园
So, GPS put your driver at Morningside Park
逗留了至少25分钟
for a window of 25 minutes last night,
正是某位俄罗斯人
right around the time
中枪身亡的时段
some Russian guy succumbs to acute lead poisoning.
你觉得那位出租车司机
And you think our cab driver
和这起谋杀案有关
is connected to this homicide?
我还以为你能告诉我
Figured you could tell me.
还有  为什么特勤局要掺和
Along with, why are the secret service crawling
这起调查
all over this investigation?
我不知道
I have no idea.
要是你能调查出的话就太好了
But whatever you can find out would be much appreciated.
不太可能
Unlikely,
鉴于他们跟你们一样
considering they're about as forthcoming
不太爱分享信息
with information as you are.
我尽力而为吧
I'll see what I can find out.
死于公园的俄罗斯人那里有什么发现  芬奇
So what do we know about the dead Russian in the park, Finch?
瓦蒂姆・普什科夫
Vadim Pushkov.
如果牵涉到了特勤局
If the secret service is involved,
那他有可能是国际罪犯
he's likely some kind of international criminal.
看来这位司机昨晚载错了人
Seems like our cabbie gave the wrong guy a ride last night.
从59街大桥走  去皇后区
Take the 59th Street bridge into Queens.
你有地址吗
Do you have an address?
没有地址
No address.
只管开
Just go.
我似乎没法黑进这个女人的手机
I can't seem to access this woman's phone.
她不是没有手机
Either she doesn't have one,
就是处于关机状态
or it's currently turned off.
他们要过桥去皇后区
They're taking the Bridge into Queens.
一直往下开
Now take this all the way down
在弗农街右转
and make a right on Vernon.
我有不祥的预感  芬奇
Got a bad feeling about this, Finch.
这里右转
Turn right up here.
她要去的地方很奇怪
Strange place for her to be going.
在单行道的岔口转弯了
One-way street that bottlenecks down the way.
就停在这吧
This is good right here.
他们停在路当中了
They're stopped in the middle of the block.
她在引他到无人烟处  芬奇
She's isolated him, Finch.
11.5美元
$11.50.
首先  问几个问题
First, a few questions.
抱歉
Excuse me?
我有个朋友昨晚坐了你的车
A friend of mine was in your cab last night.
你认得他吗
Do you recognize him?
我每天都要见很多人
I see a lot of people... every day.
他叫普什科夫  你载过他
Pushkov. You drove him.
他有落下什么东西吗
Did he leave anything behind?
别对我说谎
Do not lie to me.
女士
Look, lady,
我每晚都交班
I turn in the cab every night.
如果有人落了东西
If someone did leave anything in here,
我找不到的
I didn't find it.
清理掉
抱歉  不载客了
Sorry, I'm not in service.
事情是这样的
Here's the thing.
你还是载我一程吧
You're gonna want to give me a lift anyway.
我今天倒霉透了  知道不
Listen, I'm having a pretty lousy day, okay?
你还是  下车好吧
You mind, uh, just getting out?
恐怕你会碰到更倒霉的  费尔曼
I'm afraid it's gonna get a whole lot worse, Fermin.
我不想惹麻烦
I don't want any trouble.
不幸的是  这点上你我都没有发言权
Unfortunately, you and I don't have much to say on that matter.
现在听好了
Now listen up.
我们被围堵了  大概有两辆车
We're about ready to be boxed in by two cars.
四到六个枪手
Four to six shooters.
我需要你瞄准他们车的后围侧板
I want you to aim for the rear quarter panel of their car,
不要熄火  明白了吗
and don't let off the gas, you got that?
就是现在  费尔曼
Now's a good time, Fermin.
-等等  什么  -快  费尔曼
- Wait, what? - Now, Fermin.
里瑟先生  你没事吧
Mr. Reese, are you okay?
我没事  芬奇
I'm fine, Finch.
但是真正的威胁找上门了
But I think the real threat just found us.
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
他们是什么人
Who are those people?
里瑟先生  那个把他引入陷阱的金发女人
Mr. Reese, the blonde who led him into the trap
一下车就打了个电话
made a call just after leaving the cab.
我没法完整辨别
I can't quite make it out.
但我确信她讲的是爱沙尼亚语
But I believe it's Estonian.
爱沙尼亚黑帮
Estonian mob.
我认出他们的手法了
I recognize their methods.
围杀
It was a kill box.
在俄罗斯有过类似经历
Had a similar experience in Russia.
对他们来说效果不佳
Didn't work out too well for them.
关掉GPS
Disabled the GPS.
不能冒险让他们追踪到你
Can't risk them accessing it to track you down.
你是谁
Who are you?
搭车人
Just a guy who needed a ride.
那个女人问了你昨天载的一个乘客
That woman asked about a passenger in your cab last night.
他叫普什科夫  他怎么了
His name is Pushkov. What happened to him?
我不认识这个普什科夫
I don't know this Pushkov!
我只是个出租车司机
I'm just a cab driver!
怎么  你还要像对那个女人一样对我撒谎吗
What, you're gonna lie to me like you lied to that woman?
我们可大不相同  费尔曼
There's a big difference here, Fermin.
我是唯一能够帮你的人  明白吗
I'm the only one who can help you, you understand?
那你是为什么要帮我
So why are you helping me?
也许是因为你是个正常的人
Maybe you're an honest guy
只是犯了点小错误
who just made a mistake.
但你得想清楚  你生命的价值是否
But you need to decide whether your life's worth more
比那人落在出租车里的东西高
than whatever that guy left in your cab.
好吧
Okay.
我在机场载上这个人
I picked this guy up near the airport, huh?
我们开了好一会儿  他看起来很紧张
We drove around for a while. He seemed nervous.
他用俄语打电话
He spoke in Russian on his cell phone.
-你懂俄语吗  -一点点
- You understand Russian? - A little.
我小时候在古巴  我祖父说俄语
My grandfather spoke it when I was a kid in Cuba.
听起来他是想要卖掉什么东西
It sounded like he was trying to sell something.
他说  "H说"
He called it, uh, "H-said,"
还说什么  "旅客"
Or--or--or "Travelers".
我不知道他在讲什么
I didn't know what he was talking about.
那个金发女人说他落了东西在你车上
That blonde lady said he left something in your cab.
是什么
What was it?
我不是警察  费尔曼
I'm not a cop here, Fermin,
但如果你想要我帮你  你得告诉我
But if you want my help, you need to tell me
他落了什么在你车里
what he left in your cab.
一台手提电脑
He left a laptop.
他落在座位下面了
He left it underneath the seat.
肯定是忘了拿
He must have forgot.
你怎么处理的
What'd you do with it?
卖了
I sold it...
卖给一个朋友换钱了
to a friend for money.
我本来不是这种人  但是
Look, I never do that, but--
我载着他开了一天
I drive him around all day
然后他居然没付钱
and then he stiffed me on the tab.
-芬奇  你在吗  -永远都在  里瑟先生
- Finch, are you there? - Always, Mr. Reese.
看来普什科夫做了笔交易
Sounds like this Pushkov had some kind of a deal
把手提电脑卖给了爱沙尼亚帮
to sell the laptop to the Estonians.
但他却落在了出租车上
But then he leaves it in the cab?
他知道会有危险
He knew it would be dangerous.
他是想谈个更高的价钱
He wanted to negotiate a higher price.
显然  爱沙尼亚帮可没心情议价
Clearly, the Estonians were in no mood to negotiate.
那台手提电脑上会有什么东西
What in the world could be on that laptop?
-你在跟谁说话  -我的合伙人
- Who are you talking to? - My business partner.
爱沙尼亚帮不在乎手提电脑是不是在他手上
Estonians don't care if he doesn't have the laptop.
他们杀他是因为他知情
They'll kill him just because he knew about it.
就为了一台手提电脑
Just because of a laptop?
是为了手提电脑里的东西  把它找回
Because of what was on it, and getting it back
可能是保你小命的唯一筹码
may be the only leverage we have to keep you alive.
先从你负责出售的朋友开始
Let's start with the friend you sold it to.
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：阿好  芒果妖怪  灰灰是菇凉  寒小冰的非小燕  板栗桑
■
时间轴：擦擦  烟幕迟迟
特效&后期：灰灰是菇凉   校对&总监： 阿好
■
芬奇  看来爱沙尼亚帮已经来过了
Finch, looks like the Estonians have been here already.
阿齐兹
Aziz?
很遗憾  费尔曼
Sorry, Fermin.
是我把手提电脑卖给他的
I sold him the laptop.
是我害他被杀的
I got him killed.
-手提电脑还在吗  -应该不在了
- Is the laptop still here? - I don't think so.
他告诉我他今早找到了一个买家
He told me he found a buyer this morning.
他把钱分我了
He paid me my share.
曼索尔先生在被爱沙尼亚帮
Mr. Mansoor sold the laptop
杀害之前就卖掉了手提电脑
before his demise at the hands of the Estonians.
他们为了找电脑把这里翻了个底朝天
They trashed this place looking for it.
他们怎么找到这里的
How'd they know to come here?
普什科夫可能在电脑上装了
Pushkov may have installed a beacon
开机启动的指示器
that turns on when you power it up.
任何人只要有访问代码
Anyone with an access code
就能追踪它的位置
could follow it geographically.
而只要有人接触到那台电脑
And they're willing to kill anyone
他们就会杀了他
who comes in contact with it.
我黑进了阿齐兹的电子邮箱
I've gotten into Aziz's email account.
这里显示他把手提电脑卖给了
It appears that he sold the laptop
一个名叫D3MN8的线上买家
to an online buyer named "D3MN8."
有什么方法能找到他吗
Any way we can track him?
如果D3MN8发现了电脑上的东西
If D3MN8 discovers what's on the laptop,
他会尝试浏览文件
he may try to flip it.
在这种情况下  他可能会去地下网络
In which case, he'd probably go to the darknet,
在"丝绸之路"或者
try to sell it on Silk Road
其他黑市论坛卖掉它
or one of those black market forums.
我会试着追踪他
I'll try to track him down,
看能否安排一次会面
see if I can negotiate a meeting.
阿齐兹怎么办
What about Aziz?
纽约警方会很快到这里
The NYPD will be here shortly...
查出杀害你朋友的凶手
find out who did this to your friend.
我们还是走吧
We better get moving.
因为你就是他们下一个目标
'cause you're gonna be next.
让我猜猜
Let me guess,
那位司机招认了
your driver confessed
是他在公园里杀了那俄罗斯人
to killing the Russian in the park.
不尽然
Not exactly.
你想听好消息还是坏消息
You want the good news or the bad news?
先说好消息吧
Start with the good.
普什科夫是被爱沙尼亚黑帮杀的
Pushkov was killed by the Estonian mob.
他们在找他落在出租车上的手提电脑
They're chasing a laptop he left in our driver's cab.
所以特勤局的人才会蜂拥而至
Which explains the secret service swarming the body.
他们为什么迫切想得到那台手提电脑
Why do they want this laptop so bad?
还不清楚  可他们不惜
Don't know yet, but they're willing
杀死所有接触过的人
to kill anyone who comes in contact with it.
留意一个金发女人
Keep an eye out for a blonde.
她是负责人
She runs point for them.
我会调出爱沙尼亚帮的分析资料
I'll pull our analytical brief on the Estonians.
现在告诉我坏消息吧
Now, what's the bad news?
他们刚扔下另一具尸体
They just dropped another body.
我会短信发你地址
I'll text you the address.
我真不该拿走那台手提电脑
I never should have taken that laptop.
我就知道这整件事都是个错误
I knew this whole thing was a mistake!
不管我做什么  到头来都不对
No matter what I do, nothing seems to turn out right.
你是指  你是怎么决定
You mean, how you chose to get involved
和门多萨这样的走私贩扯上关系的
with a smuggler like Mendoza?
什么   门多萨是我们的联系人
Wh--Mendoza was our contact.
我们逃出来后
When we defected,
他就为我们这些棒球手安排好一切
he arranged everything for us ballplayers.
他把我们一路带到纽约
He brought us all the way to New York.
作为回报  你们挣的钱要分给他
In exchange, he takes a cut of your contract when you get paid?
门多萨说这是规矩
Mendoza said that's the way it worked.
他承诺得天花乱坠
He promises the moon.
我以为棒球  这个国家
I thought baseball, this country,
能让我赚到钱
was gonna make me rich,
可这个局
but this game...
你知道  取决于自己
you know, it lies to you.
你一受伤  就完了
And once you got injured, it was over.
打不了球  就赚不了钱
You can't play, you can't make money.
就变得无人问津
You become a nobody.
所以门多萨找到了另一条途径
So Mendoza figured he'd find another way
从你们身上吸金
to get his money out of you.
-你的家人  -对  他说他会帮我
- Your family. - Yeah, he said he'd help.
可现在他一味压榨我  毫不在乎
But now he's sticking it to me. He doesn't care.
有时我希望我从没离开古巴
Sometimes I wish that I'd never left Cuba.
你的所作所为很勇敢
You did a brave thing.
背井离乡  为家人谋求更好的生活
Leaving to find a better life for your family.
美国梦  不是吗
American dream, right?
找份好工作  买栋大房子
You get a good job, you buy a house.
我宁可全都不要  只要能再见家人一面
I'd trade all that in just to see my family one more time.
看着儿子长大  你知道吗
To see my son grow up, you know?
他几乎都不认识我了
He doesn't even know who I am anyway.
我可以帮你挽回  费尔曼
I can help you make things right, Fermin.
但你得信我
But you've got to trust me.
我还有选择吗
Do I have a choice?
你那个线人
This CI of yours...
他怎么知道爱沙尼亚帮杀了普什科夫
How does he know the Estonians killed Pushkov?
他们在找他带的一台手提电脑
They're hunting a laptop he had on him.
你知道里面有什么吗
You know what's on that thing?
-你知道吗  警探  -还不知道
- Do you, Detective? - Not yet.
可我有很强的预感
But I'm getting a strong premonition
里面的东西会让政府颇为尴尬
that whatever it is, it can embarrass the government.
我说得对吗
Am I right?
我只想帮忙
Look, I'm only trying to help.
瓦蒂姆・普什科夫是名独来独往的黑客高手
Vadim Pushkov was a lone wolf hacker extraordinaire.
机密
五年前我们第一次注意到他
We first noticed him five years ago.
他偷了了十万个信用卡账号
He stole over 100,000 credit card numbers.
他第二次出现时
The next time he turned up,
侵入了内华达的无人机引航站
he hacked into a drone pilot station in Nevada
把飞行控制加密协议在线出售给了
and sold the flight control encryption protocol online
一个巴基斯坦的买家
to a buyer in Pakistan.
这么说他再次出现了
So, he showed up on your radar again,
你们希望在他出售所窃资料前抓住他
and you guys hoped to catch him before he sold whatever he stole.
问题是  我们不知道
Problem is, we have no idea
普什科夫这次黑到什么了
what Pushkov was up to this time.
要是那台手提电脑
Afraid to even think about what would happen
未知号码信息
HTSC电脑店
第九东大街 3424号
误入敌手  后果不堪设想
if the contents of that laptop slipped into the wrong hands.
你跟我来吧
You might want to come with me.
去哪里
Where are we going?
在东村的一家电脑店发现一具尸体
Body dropped at a computer store in the East Village.
最后卖出那台手提电脑的人
Last guy to sell the laptop.
里瑟先生  我还在继续搜寻D3MN8
Mr. Reese, my search for D3MN8 continues.
不过我想我已经发现了
But I think I may have discovered
普什科夫手提电脑上的东西
what was on Pushkov's laptop.
是什么  芬奇
What is it, Finch?
卡特警探说
Detective Carter said
他们发现普什科夫在肯尼迪机场
they found a $275 receipt on Pushkov
短期停车的面值275块钱的收据
for short-term parking at JFK.
275块
$275?
没看出来是短期
Nothing short-term about that.
对  他没有飞往任何地方
No, and he wasn't flying anywhere.
所以如果奥多涅斯听到他说"H说"
So if Ordonez heard him say "H-said",
可能他是在说
It's possible that he's speaking about
国土安全局自动身份识别数据库
the Homeland Security automated identification database.
应该是他偷了
My best guess is he stole information
大量乘客的信息  其中包括
on a huge number of travelers:
地址  联调局清关数据  生物识别数据
Addresses, FBI clearances, biometric data.
就是说他们可以随意
Means they could sneak whoever they wanted
盗用任何人的信息入境
directly into the country using stolen credentials.
恐怖分子会想拿到这些数据
Terrorists could get their hands on this.
无人了解的情况下  漏洞才有价值
A breach like that only has value if no one knows about it.
因此他们要杀死
Which is why they're killing everybody
所有接触过手提电脑的人
that comes in contact with the laptop.
我的怀疑得到了证实
My suspicions are confirmed.
我在D3MN8常用的黑暗网络
I found the laptop listed
聊天频道发现了所列笔记本
on a darknet IRC channel frequented by D3MN8.
他要价五万美金
He's trying to sell it for $50,000.
他发现了他手里的东西
He's discovered what he's got in his hands
以及其中的价值
and what it's worth.
如果他能活下去的话
If he lives that long.
我会前去交易  安排会面
I'll try to make a buy, set up a meet.
里瑟先生  我设法和黑市上的D3MN8
Mr. Reese, I've managed to connect with D3MN8
取得了联系
on the black market.
我们已经商定好了笔记本的价格
We've agreed on a price for the laptop.
我正给你发送
Sending you the address now
我约他见面的交易地址
to meet up with him for the buy.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
芬奇  这里没人
Finch, there's no one here.
这里是空的
This place is empty.
什么意思  空的
What do you mean, empty?
屋里只有我们两个人
We may be the only ones in this room...
但并非只有我们
But we're not alone.
有人在监视我们
We're being watched.
我是弗斯科
Fusco.
鲍曼会过去接你
Bowman will swing by and pick you up.
你们俩拿上包裹  按计划送达
You two will get the package, deliver it as planned.
听着  我想过了
Hey, listen, I've been thinking about this.
我做不到
I can't do it.
我得自保
I got to keep my nose clean...
我被抓了对你也没什么好处
because I'm no good to you locked up.
我肯定我们会为你
I'm sure we'd find something for you
找到事做  莱奈尔
to do with yourself, Lionel.
另外  这样你对我也没什么好处
Besides, you're not that much good to me as it is.
不行  抱歉  我做不到
No, I'm sorry, I just can't do it.
不行  好吧  莱奈尔
No? Okay, Lionel.
你自寻死路
You've sealed your fate.
未知发件人
多数事故不需要用到工具
失踪
格里福尼  今晚
里瑟先生  我刚收到D3MN8发来的信息
Mr. Reese, I've just had a message from D3MN8.
他取消了买卖
He's called off the sale.
显然  他不喜欢你的样子
Apparently, he doesn't like the way you look.
我的样子有什么问题
What the hell's wrong with the way I look?
他说你样子像联调局的
He says you look like a Fed.
他叫停了交易
He's voided the transaction.
那台手提电脑也许是我们
That laptop may be our only hope
拯救奥多涅斯的唯一希望
of getting Ordonez's life back.
D3MN8没他自以为的那么聪明
D3MN8 isn't as smart as he thinks he is.
现在他也危在旦夕
Now he's in grave danger too.
我通过摄像机反查了他的信号
I piggybacked on the signal from his camera
追踪到了他现在的方位
and traced it back to where he is right now.
他在杨松桌球房
I have an address at Yeongson Pool Hall.
我想爱沙尼亚帮的朋友们
I guess our Estonian friends
也在找D3MN8  芬奇
are looking for D3MN8 too, Finch.
我们要耽搁会儿了
We're gonna be delayed.
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese?
我可能得自己去见D3MN8了
I might have to meet D3MN8 on my own.
想出去兜兜风吗  走吧
Want to go for a ride? Come on.
喂  莱奈尔
Yes, Lionel?
在忙吗
This a bad time?
有点
Kinda.
我稍后回你电话
I'll call you back.
格里福尼  今晚
喂
Yeah?
行  好吧
Okay, fine.
你想什么时候办
What time you want to do this?
这是我们在电脑店
This is the security camera footage
拍到的监控录像
we took from the computer store.
阿齐兹・曼索尔带着手提电脑离开
We have Aziz Mansoor leaving with the laptop.
约45分钟后  他空手而归
About 45 minutes later, he returns without it.
没有笔记本  一定是给卖了
No laptop. He must have sold it.
可你看这里
But look at this.
-20分钟后  -档案里有她
- 20 minutes later... - She's in the file.
爱沙尼亚帮的头目  名叫伊莉娜・卡普
Estonian operator named Irina Kapp.
国际刑警六个月前发布了红色通缉令
Interpol issued a red notice on her six months ago.
她走出门  十分钟后
She walks out, ten minutes later,
曼索尔先生被乱枪打死
Mr. Mansoor dies in a hail of bullets.
我们的死亡天使
Our little angel of death.
干吗
Yeah?
我来见个人
I'm here to meet someone.
你是谁
Who are you?
来干吗
And what do you want?
我带了钱
I brought the money.
但你不是他
But you're not him.
-你不是D3MN8  -你怎么知道
- You're not D3MN8. - What do you know?
我知道他就坐在那边
I know that he's sitting right over there.
想要用手机来远程操控
And if he's gonna remotely monitor a wireless camera
摄像头
with his phone,
最好把IP地址加密工作做好
he should take better care to encrypt its IP address.
你最好不要轻举妄动
You don't want to do that.
谢谢
Thank you.
坐下
Platz.
-钱拿来看看  -我没做这过种事
- Let's see the money. - I'm new at this sort of thing.
不过我想应该让我先看看手提电脑
But I'm guessing I'm supposed to see the laptop first.
你不是爱沙尼亚帮的
You're not with the Estonians.
没错  我不是
No, I'm not.
你早前想买这台手提电脑
You tried to buy the laptop earlier.
不过我不喜欢你搭档的样子
But I didn't like the way your partner looked.
所以你就跟爱沙尼亚帮做个交易
So you arranged to make a deal with the Estonians,
以为他们出价会更高
thinking they would pay more.
你错了
You'd be wrong.
十万  小额票
100,000. Small bills.
你要价的两倍
Double your asking price.
条件呢
What's the catch?
条件  阿尔伯特
The catch... Albert,
就是你要马上离开
is that you leave this very second,
消失  至少一年内不再出现
disappear, and don't show your face for at least a year.
尤其是别回到你母亲住的皇后区
Especially not at your mom's house in Queens,
也就是你目前居住的地方
where you presently reside.
拿上钱  走得远远的
Take your money and go far, far away.
有帮穷凶恶极的人想要这台手提电脑
Some very bad people want that laptop.
一旦他们知道你见过那台
And if they know you've even seen it,
他们会杀了你
they will kill you.
这就是条件  阿尔伯特
So that's the catch, Albert.
那你为什么想要
Then why would you want it?
这就不劳你费心了
Let me worry about that.
拿上你的钱
Take your money.
马上走
Go. Now.
抱歉  芬奇  刚有点事要处理
Sorry, Finch. Got distracted.
桌球房在哪  你拿到手提电脑了吗
Where's the Pool Hall? Did you get the laptop?
是的  我就在这儿
Yes, I'm here,
拿到手提电脑了  里瑟先生
and I have the laptop, Mr. Reese.
不过恐怕你得赶紧过来
But I'm afraid you'd better come rather quickly.
你好像拿了我的东西
I think you have something that belongs to me.
打开看过了吗
Did you open it?
没必要  我知道里面有什么
I don't have to. I know what's on it.
我不会让你拿走它的
And I know I'll never let you take it.
无论如何都不行
At any price.
我喜欢男人戴眼镜
I do like men with glasses.
真遗憾
Too bad.
打死那只狗
Shoot the dog.
要我就不会那么做  各位
I wouldn't do that, fellas.
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese!
想得美
Nice try.
扔得高了
Little high...
偏了  不过好歹打到了
and outside, but it still got there.
坐下  乖宝贝  乖宝贝
Heel. Good boy, good boy.
卡特  你错过好戏了
Hey, Carter... you missed all the fun.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
联调局刚拿到那名金发女郎的手机坐标
Feds just got a hit on that blonde woman's cell phone
在一家韩国桌球房
at a Korean pool hall.
我猜你们都在那儿吧
I'm guessing you guys are there?
赶紧撤离
So you got to clear out.
能否搭我们一程
Don't suppose you could give us a ride?
搜索执行人
弗斯科  莱奈尔
GPS三角定位
搜索执行人
弗斯科  莱奈尔
目标已找到
目标  格里福尼  卢西亚诺
搜索执行人
弗斯科  莱奈尔
目标已找到
暴力程度  92%
格里福尼  卢西亚诺
联邦证人保护
格里福尼马上就要出来了
Grifoni should be coming out soon.
未知号码
给我几分钟时间好吗  是我前妻
Hey, give me a second, will you? It's my ex.
我得告诉她
I got to tell her
今天要晚点去接小孩
I'm gonna be late picking up my kid.
好
Yeah.
我是弗斯科
Yeah, Fusco.
你好  莱奈尔
Hello, Lionel.
好久没聊了
Long time no speak.
有什么事吗
Hey, what's going on?
你先给我打的  莱奈尔  记得吗
You called me, Lionel. Remember?
我是回你电话
I'm calling you back.
不好意思
Yeah, sorry about that.
最近一直在  忙一个案子
I've been, uh, kind of buried on this case.
好吧  我们这边本来也需要你帮忙
Yeah, well, we could've used your help on this one too.
找我什么事
What do you want?
没事  没什么事
Nah, it's-- it's nothing.
不用担心  一切都好
Don't worry about it. Everything's fine.
好吧
Great.
跟你聊聊真高兴  挂了
Glad we could talk. Gotta go.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
走吧
Here we go.
你没事吧  脸色特别难看
You all right? You look like crap.
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
他来了
Here he comes.
把他带上车
We'll take him at the car.
等等  他是在笑吗
Wait a second. Is he laughing?
有什么好笑的  格里福尼
What the hell's so funny, Grifoni?
我笑是因为
I'm laughing...
挨枪子的那个不是我
'cause I ain't the one who's about to get hit.
抱歉  伙计们
Sorry, fellas.
以利亚告诉我你们可能会来
Elias told me you might be coming.
自从上次搞砸后
Ever since I screwed up,
我就一直在努力重获他的青睐
I've been trying to work my way back into his good graces.
就像你跟HR的关系一样
Kinda like you and HR.
好吧
Oh, well.
至于你
And you...
以利亚想让你带个口信
Elias wants you to take a message back
给你的朋友西蒙斯和HR
to your pal Simmons and HR.
音频拦截
主体  维克斯  雷吉娜
执行人  卡特  乔丝
找不到伊莉娜・卡普
No sign of Irina Kapp anywhere.
没人知道手提电脑的下落
And no one knows anything about the laptop.
应该还在黑市
It's still out there on the black market.
你不是图书馆员哈
You are not a librarian, huh?
不用担心你的车
Don't worry about your cab.
新车很快就到
A brand-new one's on its way.
趁我还记得
And before I forget...
今天的打车钱
I owe you cab fare for the day.
你会满意小费的
Think you're gonna like your tip.
维克斯探员
Agent Vickers,
这位先生名叫费尔曼・奥多涅斯
This gentleman's name is Fermin Ordonez.
据说他有效帮助我们
I've been told he was very instrumental
拿下了爱沙尼亚帮
in tracking down the Estonians
杀害普什科夫和曼索尔的凶手
who killed Pushkov and Mansoor.
感谢您的帮助
Thank you for your help.
不客气
You're welcome.
听说他手上有似乎有
It also sounds like he may have something
你一直在寻找的东西
you've been looking for.
真的吗
Really?
在哪
Where is it?
或许他能拿给我们
Maybe he can get it to us,
只要我们帮他解决一点事情
if we can help him out with something.
什么事情
And what's that?
只需要一点点钱
It'll just take a little bit of money
以及一些海岸警卫队的帮忙
and some help from the Coast Guard.
不敢相信你真的来了
我也是
会接球吗
不知道你是怎么办成的
Don't know how you pulled that one off.
感觉肯定不错
It sure feels good.
确实
Yeah.
我自有妙招
I got my own bag of tricks.
看来是
Guess so.
不过我得问问你
But I have to ask you...
莱奈尔最近是怎么了
what's going on with Lionel?
什么意思
What do you mean?
没什么
No reason.
我会看着他的
I'll keep an eye on him.
谢了
Thanks.
当时到底怎么回事
What the hell happened out there?
你说呢
You tell me.
他们知道我们冲他去的
'Cause they knew we were coming for him.
我们被出卖了
We got double-crossed.
我不明白的是
The part I don't get...
他们杀死了鲍曼
they shot Bowman,
却让你活了下来
but they let you just walk away.
因为他们想让我给HR带个口信
'Cause they want me to send HR a message.
以利亚说  去死吧
Elias said, "Go to hell."
坦白说  我有同感
Quite frankly, I second the motion.
卡特
Carter.
等等  你是谁
Wait. Who is this?
什么意思
What do you mean by that?
等等  别挂
Wait, hold on.
-怎么了  -匿名线报
- What's that about? - Anonymous tip.
-什么线报  -戴维森
- About what? - Davidson.
去年二月失踪的那名内务部警探
The IA detective that disappeared last February.
说他被谋杀了  是个警察干的
Said he was murdered... by another cop.